Hi there. These next few lessons we'll give you a broad overview of mutual funds,
大家好接下来的几节课将大致讲解共同基金
hedge funds, and exchange traded funds.
对冲基金和交易所交易基金
The second half will be a deep dive into portfolio optimization,
第二部分将深入讲解投资组合优化
which is really exciting because it will help you build the
这部分内容很精彩
mathematical skill sets that you'll want to have as a quant.
将帮助你掌握量化分析师必备的数学技能
Now, I have to admit that math tends to scare me sometimes.
说实话 数学有时候让我有点恐惧
Well actually, okay, math always scares me a lot.
实际上一直都让我很恐惧
But math is also very cool.
但数学实际上很有趣
When you learn the math,
学习数学后
its like gaining superpowers that let you extract meaning from the chaos of numbers.
就好像掌握了超能力 使你能从杂乱的数字中发现有意义的规律
With that said, we'd still like to acknowledge that
但是 不得不承认
diving into the math can still feel scary or overwhelming,
学习数学依然让人感到亚历山大
especially when you feel like it's just you alone in a library or a coffee shop.
尤其是一个人在图书馆或咖啡厅苦苦专研时 更让人苦闷
I've been through several Eudacity Nano degrees as a student,
我以学员身份学习了多门纳米学位课程
and I also felt like sometimes it was just me and my computer in a library.
我有时候也觉得图书馆只有我和电脑
I'd like to share a bit of advice for getting through
下面说几条建议 可以帮助你
the more challenging material in an online learning environment.
顺利掌握在线学习中更有挑战的知识
What really helped me get through some of
对我来说 真正帮助我学习疑难内容的方法是
the more challenging subjects was reaching out online to interact with my classmates.
上网与同学交流
I'd either ask questions when I was stuck,
当我遇到问题时 我就会去论坛提问
or tried to answer other student questions.
还尝试回答其他学员的问题
I would also post curriculum suggestions,
我也会发布课程大纲建议
and sometimes I'd get a response from someone at Eudacity.
有时候会收到优达学城员工的建议
Whether your online chats directly answered the question you're trying to solve,
在线聊天可以直接回答你要解决的问题
they help you by building a community that supports you,
他们为你打造了一个支持社区
and also motivates you.
并且可以激励你
It's one of the important side benefits that you've
这是现场课程的重要优势之一
already experienced when you take in-person classes,
你已经体验过
because you're surrounded by other people with shared goals and shared experiences,
你周围都是有着共同目标和共同经验的其他人
because they have empathy for you and your struggles.
他们理解你的难处
In the Eudacity classroom,
在优达学城教室中
your classmates and mentors are there with you too just connected by modern technology.
你身边也有学员和导师 他们只是通过现代科技与你沟通
Also, we want to remind you that there's a whole team of people at Eudacity,
此外 优达学城有一整个团队
many of whom may not necessarily be on camera,
都会在你的学习之旅中协助你
that are working to support you on your journey.
他们不一定会出现在镜头中
We encourage you to regularly connect with your fellow classmates so that
建议你定期与其他学员联系
you can support each other on your journey through the program.
大家共同努力 顺利从这门课程中毕业